thank you you are the founder of power
of the Lamb Ministries yep and you have
an interesting interesting Journey after
our music for this evening we'd like to
hear about that Journey um we have
Stephanie Dawn with us and she's going
to play the uh she's going to sing and
she's going to be accompanied by Dan
Thornton she's going to sing
speechless speechless thank you
Stephanie Dawn for that that lovely song
it's
lovely Pastor Meyers let's get to it as
Danny says let's cut this
melon you know
you have a journey that in a sense is
kind of similar to mine in that we were
both in the music industry tell us about
your Beginnings even before you got into
the music industry did you grow up in a
Christian home what was your home home
life like so I was born in Jamaica um I
didn't grow up in you know we weren't a
a religious family like going to church
every uh week or anything like that I
mean we went to church sometimes but it
was uh my parents you know good people
taught us to be respectful all those
things so we grew up in a good home um
my introduction to Christianity kind of
came in
stages uh beginning with with when I was
around 12 years old I had you know an
experience um with um a cousin of mine
who came over to the states and
introduced me to the Bible introduced me
to the Book of Revelation and really
like scared me to to death that was your
introduction to the Bible the Book of
Revelation that was my I don't know if
you want to hear the story but uh it yes
go ahead tell us um so I was uh I was I
was 12 no I was actually 11 I sorry I
was 12 my brother was
11 and you know like I said we didn't go
to church too often or whatever and my
cousin comes from England uh she's about
14 years old her name is Susan and uh
Susan uh would talk to us about the
Bible we just fell in love with her
immediately I mean we just got really
connected it was our first time meeting
her and by this time we were in the
states we were in America um so Susan
one one morning is talking to us about
the Bible as she usually did but this
time she's talking to us about this
thing called the mark of the
beast and my parents weren't at home at
the time they were out wherever and it
was just me my brother and Susan at home
and you know she's telling us about this
thing in the Book of Revelation called
the mark of the beast and my brother and
I as she's talking my brother and I are
like oh no no this can't be happening
this can't be happening why because uh
that
summer we had just watched a movie about
a little boy who discovers he's the
Antichrist oh no and he was from England
as far as I remember oh no and uh he has
666 written in his forehead and so
anyone that discovers his identity dies
a
horrendous just
painful like just crazy death like
getting hit by a truck and the truck
doesn't kill yet and then a crow comes
out of nowhere and it's and they're just
like and like their death would just be
so horrendous so after we saw that movie
my brother and I decided that we never
wanted to know what the mark of the
beast is wow and that was your
introduction that was my introduction
man my cousin's like I know what the
mark of the beast is do you want to know
what the mark of the beast is and I'm
thinking we are about to die like we are
about to die and then she proceeds to
tell us uh that there are certain
there's a certain company that produces
soap I'm not going to mention the name
of company and on their soap boxes is
this symbol of a circle with a half moon
and a man's face in it I don't know if
you've ever heard that before I know
which one you're talking about and she
was like that is the mark of the beast
oh no and I'm thinking we are about to
die and my parents aren't home and then
she's like do you have a soap box in
your house and I'm like yes Susan we
have a soap box in the house and she's
like where where is it and my brother I
like it's in the basement and she's like
let's go and so off we go down the steps
and the steps are creaking and in my
mind I hear the horror music in the
background like things are about to end
we get down to the basement and we point
to the soap box and we start backing up
and she's moving to the Soap Box she
picks it up she turns it she looks at it
and then she looks at us and she's like
there it is
my brother and I see the circle with the
half moon and the man's face in it we
run out the house screaming in our
pajamas wow we are standing in the
middle of the street no laughing on the
set please we are standing in the middle
of the street screaming New York this is
in Freeport Long Island long we are
screaming and crying and my cousin is
laughing to death oh and I'm sure there
was people outside we're looking for
Crows we're looking for houses to fall
we're looking for the earth to open up
and like after like 5 minutes of nothing
happening we kind of calm down and that
was my introduction to the Book of
Revelation you know it's and the Bible
it's funny but it's not funny it's funny
in the you know the way you're telling
it but it's not funny in that it's it's
such a distortion of what the true mark
of the beast is and isn't it interesting
how media can just change change how we
perceive things y it it planted a seed
in my mind after I was like okay we're
still alive nothing has happened maybe
you can know what the mark of the beast
is and live you know so I remember a
seed being planted and again it wasn't
like it wasn't like I suddenly got
interested in the Bible it was just like
a seed was planted and then I went on as
usual you know just living my life or
whatever um and so um as a teenager my
brother and I got really involved in the
hip-hop industry or in into hip-hop I
should say break dancing and just the
whole culture and by the time we got to
high school we had formed a Forman hip
hop group um we um graduated went to
college and in my second year of
college enter a talent show uh at Howard
University in Washington DC we came in
first place in that talent show wow and
that led to a recording contract with
Emi records in 19
1993 uh the name of our group was the
boogy monsters and uh we started
recording we recorded an album and while
we were recording that first album uh I
was introduced to the gospel and uh
that's where my whole life just you know
took a turn um and I ended up leaving
the music industry as well as my brother
who was in the group with us uh both of
us left the industry for the same
reason and um went into Ministry now now
I it was not my intent to go into
Ministry I just left the group because
what the things that I had learned so
impacted me that um you know I was
willing to walk away from you know
$800,000 contract and um basically went
to work at Target um you know making
like minimum wage yeah and uh hadn't
really thought about becoming a pastor
just knew that I could not continue
doing doing what I was doing um and then
from there the Lord just began to show
me different things and one thing led to
another and now here I am wow wow